This is the unit for you,
my friend.
Sturdy construction,
tons of storage compartments.
Some big enough
to fit a grown man.
- What?
- Oh, yeah.
I got in there myself once.
My roommate bet me five bucks
that I couldn't
and then he stuck a board
through the handles
and locked me in. Yeah.
It was funny till I started
feeling like I was in a coffin.
No, you...you can't fit
in that thing.
That's not deep enough.
Oh, yeah?
If I can't..
...I'll knock five bucks
off the price of the unit.
Alright, you have
yourself a deal.
Okay.
'See? I told you.'
'Sometimes, I come in here
just to get away from it.'
'Hey, a nickel!'
Oh, my God!
(Joey)
'What?'
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
What happened?
Aw, man. He promised
he wouldn't take the chairs!
What the hell happened?
How were you locked in?
And where the hell
is all of our stuff?
Well, this guy came by
to look at the unit
and, and he said he
didn't think it was big enough
to fit a grown man.
So...you got in
voluntarily?
I was trying
to make a sale!
Oh, man,
if I ever run
into that guy again,
y-you know what I'm gonna do?
Bend over?